W.A.C. Bennett fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- 1954 Official files, 1914 - 1963; F-55-29; 25 cm of textual records
  - University of British Columbia (36-1) - Letters, financial statements, reports. Letters from: Norman A.M. MacKenzie, L.W. Shemilt, Robert W. Bonner, 1954 - 1963; F-55-29-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
- 1955 Official files, 1952 - 1968; F-55-30; 18 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1955. The records reflect topics such as Attorney General, B.C. Electric, B.C. Power Commission, Highways, Oil Pipeline and P.G.E. Railway. Included are correspondence, statistics, reports, balance sheets, memoranda and speeches.
  - Attorney-General--Motor Vehicle (2-7) - Letters, statistics, report. Letters from: Robert W. Bonner, G.A. Spring, Eugene T. Parker, H.S. Ferris, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - B.C. Electric (3-1) - Letters, press releases, speech, pamphlet, photograph, report. Letters from: W.C. Mainwaring, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Letters, financial statistics, reports. Letters from: A.G. Markin, T.H. Crosby, H.J. MacLeod, Wesley D. Black, H.H. Griffin, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Letters, documents, printed material, press releases, speech, draft of speech, statistics. Letters from: George E. McKnight, T.H. Crosby, Robert E. Sommers, H.J. MacLeod, Norman Sewell, M. Baldwin, W.C. Mainwaring, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Letters, printed material, statement, report, documents. Letters from: J.H. Crosby, H.J. MacLeod, H.L. Briggs, J.N. Alsen, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Report, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - E (9) - Letter. Letters from: Charlie Ennals, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - Finance Minister (10-3) - Speech, letter (carbon copy), 1955; F-55-30-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - HA-HE (14) - Letter (carbon copy), 1955; F-55-30-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - HF-HZ (15) - Letter. Letters from: Lawrence T. Higgins, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - Highways--Deputy and Department (15-2) - Letters, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - Oil Pipeline--Gas and Gas Prices (27-2) - Letters, telegrams, financial statistics, statements, document (copy). Letters from: Homer Stevens, D.P. MacDonald, Lloyd K. Turner, J.J. Ladd, C. Farquharson, Robert W. Bonner, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters, telegrams, reports, brief (printed). Letters from: J.D. Verkerk, W. McLeod, R.F.P. Bowman, A. N. Eidse, R.V. Curiston, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Reports, memorandum, letters. Letters from: R.F.P. Bowman. (File probably kept in Premier's safe.), 1955; F-55-30-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters, telegrams, reports, memorandum. Letters from: John A. Hastings, A.P. Withall, R.A. Pennington, Ralph Chetwynd, R.F.P. Bowman. (File probably kept in Premier's safe.), 1955; F-55-30-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - P.G.E. Extension File (28-2) - Report, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - P.G.E. Railway--Statistical Material and Board Meetings (28-2) - Reports, balance sheets, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - Press Clippings (28-5) - Newspaper clippings, pamphlets, newsletters, photocopies, press release. (File opened Jan. 1, 1955.), 1952 - 1968; F-55-30-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - South Okanagan--Kelowna-Okanagan Lake Bridge (34-5) - Letter (carbon copy), 1955; F-55-30-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, 1955; F-55-30-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-49)
- 1956 Official files, 1956 - 1972; F-55-31; 26 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1956. The records reflect correspondence with Members elected in 1956 (years are cumulated), B.C. Electric, B.C. Power Commission, Federal Departments, Finance, P.G.E. Railway and Power Development. Included are correspondence, documents, reports, minutes, statistics and speeches.
  - Atlin Constituency Association (2-4) - Letters, map, telegram, press release. Letters from: Thos. J. Kirkwood., 1956 - 1972; F-55-31-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - Atlin Member--W.J. Asselstin (SC) (2-4) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Robert W. Bonner, W.J. Asselstine, 1956 - 1960; F-55-31-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - B.C. Electric (3-1) - Letters, speech, printed material. Letters from: W.C. Mainwaring, A.E. Grauer, J.H. Crosby, L.E. Cook, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - B.C. Power Commission--Correspondence (3-2) - Letters, document, report, press release, telegrams, speech, file notes. Letters from: Norman Terry, T.H. Crosby, J.A. Alinger, R.E. Stavert, W.R. Eckbert, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - B.C. Power Commission--Correspondence (3-2) - Letters, document, report. Letters from: R.A. Percival, Mrs. R.A. Percival, G. Hill, H.J. MacLeod, J.A. Young, John Sankey, Donald G. Vogel, R.M. MacDonald, Ralph E. Reading, H.F. Angus, Wesley D. Black, T.H. Crosby, R.E. Stravert, A.M. Morrison, A.C. Irving, George E. Hills, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - B.C. Power Commission--Orders-in-Council (3-2) - Letters, minutes. Letters from: T.H. Crosby, H.J. MacLeod, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - Burnaby Member--Cedric Cox (CCF), Gordon H. Dowding (CCF), and James G. Lorimer (NDP) (4-4) - Letters. Letters from: Cedric Cox, James G. Lorimer, 1957 - 1971; F-55-31-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - Comox Member--Dan Campbell (SC) (7-3) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Dan Campbell. (File opened 1956.), 1957 - 1960; F-55-31-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - Comox Member--Dan Campbell (SC) (7-3) - Letters, telegrams, newpaper clippings. Letters from: Dan Campbell, Rev. J.E. Campbell, Delbert Doll, 1961 - 1972; F-55-31-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - Federal Departments (10-1) - Telegrams, letters, press release. Letters from: C.D. Howe, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Financial statistics, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - Grand Forks-Greenwood Member--Lois Haggen (CCF) - Letters, petition. Letters from: Lois Haggen, 1956 - 1962; F-55-31-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - Peace River Member--Stanley Cornell (SC), H.E. Roche (SC), and J.F. Huhn (SC) (28-1) - Letters, telegrams, speech. Letters from: Stanley Cornell, H.E. Roche, J.F. Huhn, J.F. Stabler, 1957 - 1966; F-55-31-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-50)
  - P.G.E. Railway--Statistical Material and Board Meetings (28-2) - Balance sheets, minutes, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
  - P.G.E. Railway--Inaugural Run from Vancouver (28-2) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Geo. C. Bradley, David Kinnear, Peter W. Bell, H.J. White, David M. Armstrong, Wentworth Brown, J.W. Decker, W.M. Kirkpatrick, R.B. Sutherland, W.H. Raikes, William Clancey, E.W. Hamber, Howard Johns, D.N.W. Grubb, W. Manson, R.G. Miller, H. Anscomb, T.H. Crosby, J.N. Baird, F.H. Keefe, H.B. Twiss, Hector Crombie, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
  - P.G.E. Railway--Northern Extension Federal Aid (28-2) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Leon Balcer, James R. Nelson, George Hees, E. Davie Fulton, George C. Nowlan, J.W. Pickersgill. (File probably kept in Premier's safe.), 1956 - 1966; F-55-31-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Letters, reports. Letters from: Laverne Baldwin, T.R.B. Adams, Robert W. Bonner, Jean Lesage, W.C. Mainwaring, I. Ingledow, Willis T. Batcheller, F.E. Coy, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
  - Prince Rupert Member--W.H. Murray (SC) (29-1) - Letters, telegrams, petition, file notes. Letters from: W.H. Murray, 1957 - 1961; F-55-31-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
  - Prince Rupert Member--W.H. Murray (SC) (29-1) - Letters, telegrams, photographs. Letters from: W.H. Murray, 1962 - 1972; F-55-31-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
  - Rossland-Trail Member--Donald L. Brothers (SC) (32-1) - Letters, telegrams, report. Letters from: Donald L. Brothers, 1959 - 1963; F-55-31-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
  - Skeena Member--Hugh A. Shirreff (SC) and Dudley G. Little (SC) (34-1) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Hugh A. Shirreff, Dudley G. Little, Wesley D. Black, 1958 - 1972; F-55-31-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, list, financial statistics, telegram, 1956; F-55-31-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-51)
- 1957 Official files, 1949 - 1963; F-55-32; 9 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1957. The records reflect topics such as the B.C. Power Commission, P.G.E. Railway and Power Development. Included are correspondence, financial statistics, reports, minutes, maps and speeches.
  - B.C. Power Commission--Correspondence (3-2) - Letters. Letters from: J.H. Crosby, R.N. Donselaar, F.J. Hume, 1957; F-55-32-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - B.C. Power Commission--Orders-in-Council (3-2) - Letters. Letters from: J.H. Crosby, 1957; F-55-32-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - Cariboo Member--William Speare (SC) (5-2) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: William Speare, Sam Annett. (File opened December 1957.), 1957 - 1963; F-55-32-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences (10-1) - Letters, telegrams, financial statistics, report. Letters from: C.R. Lamoureux, 1957; F-55-32-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - Legislature--Speaker and Clerk (20-1) - Plan, informational package, 1949 - 1957; F-55-32-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters, map, report, file note. Letters from: J.S. Broadbent, Gordon M. Shrum, L.J. Bjornson, Einar M. Gunderson, Grant E. Dale, N.F. Cowdell, R.W. DeMott, S.M. Frankland, Edwin F. Peet, Cy Westaway, 1957; F-55-32-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - P.G.E. Railway--Statistical Material and Board Meetings (28-2) - Minutes, reports, 1957; F-55-32-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Letters, maps. Letters from: W.H. Collins, Harry V. Warren, Walter C. Koerner, R.B. Anderson, 1957; F-55-32-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - SA-SI (33) - Memorandum (carbon copy), 1957; F-55-32-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, 1957; F-55-32-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
- 1958 Official files, 1950 - 1971; F-55-33; 9 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1958. Included are correspondence, minutes, a list and budgets.
  - AM-AZ (2) - Letters (carbon copies), resolution (photocopy), report (photocopy), 1950 - 1963; F-55-33-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - CH-CN (6) - Letters, report, brochure, memorandum. Letters from: William Clancey, A. Cheverton, E. Choukalus, R.A. Pennington, Ronald B. Worley, Lionel A. Hartshorne, Doris Bagshawe, J. Walsh, Eva Chambers, Louis K. Christensen, Eniz L. Clarke, Wesley D. Black, W.M. Chalk, Wells Ritchie, G. Champ, A. Chadwick, Harry P. Hillen, Jacob Hoogland, E.B. Clark, John Wilford, H.G. Palmer, K. Keetch, Marion G. Daubney, J. Edward Read, E.H. Rice, L.M. Wenham, 1958; F-55-33-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Pamphlet, 1958; F-55-33-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - P.G.E. Railway--Statistical Material and Board Meetings (28-2) - Minutes, statement, list, 1958 - 1961; F-55-33-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-52)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Budgets, 1958 - 1971; F-55-33-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Operating budgets, 1958 - 1971; F-55-33-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Letters, pamphlet. Letters from: A.E. Gauer, Walter C. Koerner, G.E. Elkington, Glen E. Braden, Jania Kania, 1958; F-55-33-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6), 1958; F-55-33-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6), 1958; F-55-33-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
- 1959 Official files, 1959 - 1967; F-55-34; 11 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1959. The records reflect topics such as the Federal Departments, Federal-Provincial Conferences, Canada's Centenary, Peace River, P.G.E. Railway and Power Development. Included are correspondence, financial statistics, reports, resolutions, statements and speeches.
  - B.C. Electric (3-1) - Pamphlets, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - BI-BQ (4) - Telegram, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - Federal Departments (10-1) - Reports, minutes, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences (10-1) - Financial statistics, letters, resolutions, reports, minutes. Letters from: Colin A. Campbell, Keith Deacon, Gowan T. Guest, John G. Diefenbaker, Maurice Lamontagne, R.F. Shaw, Paul Bienvenu, L.J. Wallace, Lester B. Pearson, Dufferin Roblin, George R. Pearkes, M.S. Adeane, Paul Martin, Julian Scheer, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences (10-1) - Papers prepared for Ministers of Finance, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - Canada's Centenary (10-1) - Letters. Letters from: T.C. Douglas, Donald M. Fleming, Alvin Hamilton, John G. Diefenbaker, 1959 - 1967; F-55-34-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-53)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Minutes, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Peace River Power Development (28-1) - Letters, pamphlets, statements, reports, telegram. Letters from: W.C. Mainwaring, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letter, telegram. Letters from: Clifton H. Parker, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Letters, pamphlets. Letters from: F.J. Bartholomew, Gray Turgeon, Tom Reid, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: E.J. Broome, W. Ross Macdonald, Lester B. Pearson, Donald M. Fleming, E.D. Fulton, Clarence C. Dill, 1959 - 1962; F-55-34-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, 1959; F-55-34-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
- 1960 Official files, 1950 - 1971; F-55-35; 7 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1960. The records reflect topics such as the Oil Pipeline, P.G.E. Railway, Pacific Northern Railway and Power Development. Included are correspondence with members elected in 1960 (years are cumulated), other correspondence, reports, press releases, minutes, memoranda and speeches.
  - Delta Member--Camille Mather (CCF) and James H. Rhodes (CCF) (8-1) - Letters. Letters from: Camille Mather, James H. Rhodes. (File opened 1960.), 1961 - 1963; F-55-35-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Dewdney Member--David Barrett (CCF); Coquitlam Member--David Barrett (NDP) (8-2) - Letters, petition. Letters from: David Barrett. (File opened 1960.), 1961 - 1971; F-55-35-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Oil Pipeline--Gas and Gas Prices (27-2) - Reports, printed material, press release, 1960; F-55-35-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Peace River Power Development (28-1) - Pamphlet, 1960; F-55-35-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2). - Letters, telegrams, report. Letters from: Einar M. Gunderson, J.S. Broadbent, 1960; F-55-35-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - P.G.E. Railway--Statistical Material and Board Meetings (28-2) - Minutes, reports, 1960; F-55-35-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Pacific Northern Railway (28-2b) - Letters, documents (copies), list. Letters from: Bernard G. Gore, Lyle Wicks, 1960; F-55-35-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Letters, telegrams, memoranda, file notes, minutes, press releases. Letters from: M. Fraser, C. Farquharson, Robert W. Bonner, 1950; F-55-35-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, 1960; F-55-35-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-54)
- 1961 Official files, F-55-36; 18 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1961. The records reflect topics such as B.C. Electric, B.C. Energy Board, B.C. Power Commission, Peace River, P.G.E. Railway and Power Development. Included are correspondence, financial statistics, minutes, reports, file notes and speeches.
  - B.C. Electric (3-1) - Letters, telegrams, financial statistics - Gordon M. Shrum, Robert W. Bonner, James L. Ross, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - B.C. Electric (3-1) - Letters, financial statistics. Letters from: Gordon M. Shrum, Robert W. Bonner, Frank Mackenzie Ross, H.C. Alke, N.W. Swanson, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - B.C. Electric (3-1) - Financial statistics, printed material, note, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - B.C. Energy Board (3-1) - Letters, press release, financial statistics, minutes. Letters from: Gordon M. Shrum, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - B.C. Energy Board (3-1) - Computer printouts, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Letters, document (photocopy). Letters from: Robert W. Bonner, Joyce McCowan, C.J. Ferber. (File probably kept in Premier's safe.), 1961; F-55-36-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - B.C. Power Commission--Correspondence (3-2) - Letters. Letters from: Hugh L. Keenleyside, Robert W. Bonner, A. Bruce Robertson, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - B.C. Power Commission--Reports, Pamphlets, etc. (3-2) - Memoranda, financial statistics, report, map, minutes, printed material, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Budget, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - Oil Pipeline--Gas and Gas Prices (27-2) - Annual report, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - Peace River Power Development (28-1) - Report, letters, file note, pamphlet. Letters from: W.C. Mainwaring, Lord Polworth, Robert W. Bonner, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters, chart. Letters from: E. Cleven, C.E. Cleven, J.S. Broadbent, Warren Byrnell, Irene Edwards, Thomas W. Meagher, C. Jean Cameron, D. Ian Cameron, Eleanor Flemming, V. May Nezil, C.R. Filer, Janette P. Filer, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Letters, telegrams, treaty (photocopy), file notes. Letters from: Horace H. German, A.W. Toone, W.C. Mainwaring, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-55)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Letters, file notes, press releases, telegram. Letters from: Jack Phillips, Gordon M. Shrum, D.C. Fillmore, Philip A. Gaglardi, Francis Pearson, Fraser W. Bruce, Robert W. Bonner, Harry W. Young, Frank M. McMahon, H.L. Keenleyside, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - Power Development (28-9) - Statement, file notes, notes, charts, financial statistics, memorandum, press release, report, printed material, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - Provincial Premiers' Conference (29-8) - Report, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6 - Speeches, statement, 1961; F-55-36-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
- 1962 Official files, 1961 - 1972; F-55-37; 27 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1962. The records reflect topics such as B.C. Electric, B.C. Hydro, B.C. Power Commission, Finance, Oil Pipeline and Power Development. Included are correspondence, financial statistics, lists, statements, memoranda, resolutions, bonds and speeches.
  - B.C. Electric (3-1) - Letters, memoranda, essay, financial statistics, petition, lists, copy of document, printed material. Letters from: Gordon M. Shrum, Einar M. Gunderson, Robert W. Bonner, T.J. Manning, Frank Mackenzie Ross, Hugh L. Keenleyside, Artur Fouks, 1961 - 1962; F-55-37-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - B.C. Electric--Vancouver Transit Operation (3-1) - Lists, statements, pamphlets, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - B.C. Hydro and Power Authority (3-1) - Letters, memoranda, financial statistics, document, maps, list, printed material, file notes, resolution, proposal, minutes. Letters from: Hugh L. Keenleyside, W.J. Borrie, R.B. Wilson, Robert W. Bonner, Gordon M. Shrum, Einar M. Gunderson, P.R. Kidd, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - B.C. Hydro and Power Authority (3-1) - Proposal, financial statements, printed material, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - B.C. Power Commission--Correspondence (3-2) - Letters, financial statistics, printed material. Letters from: Hugh L. Keenleyside, T.H. Crosby, Clarence Wallace, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - Finance Minister (10-3) - Speech (draft), 1962; F-55-37-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-56)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Letters, telegrams, financial statistics, file notes, printed material. Letters from: Edward Townsend, W.F. Veitch, G.S. Bryson, Nigel H. Gunn, John E. Wiley, John A. Robertson, Blyth Taylor, C.F. Parshall, Dudley Dawson, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-57)
  - Finance--Deputy and Depatment (10-4) - Letters, telegrams, financial statistics, file notes, list. Letters from: Ode V. Cecil, Edward Townsend, John E. Wiley, F.D. Chapman, Leonard Walker, Joseph Pope, C.G. Fullerton, Alfred Bergman, Robert A. Hall, John F. King, Monroe Chappelear, Edward C. White, Wallace C. Latour, John F. Fennelly, Greene E. Johnson, V.M. Petroskey, Robert J. Quinn, Jerome Kohlberg Jr., Titus W. Fowler, John T. Monzani, James A. Tate, Gordon P. Osler, A.J. Milner, Nigel H. Gunn, George D. Woods, John M. Lewis, Lloyd S. Gilmour, J.H. King, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-57)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Financial statistics, notes, file notes, lists, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-57)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Printed material, charts, bonds, newsletters, speech, report, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-57)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Bulletins, 1962 - 1972; F-55-37-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-57)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Newsletters, 1962; F-55-37-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-57)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Newspaper clippings, printed material, file notes, notes, press releases, 1962 - 1964; F-55-37-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-57)